<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vadim Pidoshva</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vadim Pidoshva</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© geleus</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:38:03 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Resume Added</title>
      <link>/posts/interactive-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:38:03 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/posts/interactive-resume/</guid>
      <description>Just added an interractive resume to the &amp;ldquo;Resume&amp;rdquo; section of the website. When clicked, you will be transferred to geleus.io where I have set up a terminal-like interactive resume.
This was mainly done for fun and education purposes. Feel free to play around with it. Just note, that it is still in the development phase. I will be adding more info to it soon.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Utah County Health Department Project</title>
      <link>/projects/utah-county-health-department-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:03:15 -0700</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/utah-county-health-department-project/</guid>
      <description>This project is designed to streamline &lt;strong&gt;data organization, analysis, and security&lt;/strong&gt;, ensuring that information remains accurate, accessible, and protected. While specific details remain confidential, this post provides an overview of the key features and technical aspects of the system.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Update February 2025</title>
      <link>/posts/update-feb-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:08:25 -0700</pubDate>

      <guid>/posts/update-feb-2025/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I&amp;rsquo;m Alive! Life has been crazy these past couple of years. This post is intended to be an update on my current state of things. Also, I will try to be more consistent with managing my website—I know it has been abandoned for a while now.
Initially, this website was meant to be my personal space to share academic and personal projects. I always wanted to document, explain, and share my software for aesthetic and professional purposes.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>2023 – I&#39;m Back!</title>
      <link>/posts/2023_comeback/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:37:46 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/posts/2023_comeback/</guid>
      <description>Getting back to working on my website. Just finised my general education section last block, so, now I can fully dive into it.
So far I&amp;rsquo;m planning on working more on my personal projects for the portfolio so that I have something to present when I apply for the real job. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking to dive deeper into databases, APIs and OS. Also, haven&amp;rsquo;t been using python for A WHILE, gotta refresh it.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Image Compression</title>
      <link>/projects/image_compression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 03:28:30 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/image_compression/</guid>
      <description>Compressing images using Discrete Cosine Transform (DCT).</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition</title>
      <link>/projects/facial_recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 22:41:15 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/facial_recognition/</guid>
      <description>AI that recognizes known faces and adds unknown ones to the dataset for further training.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Online Groceries</title>
      <link>/projects/online_groceries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 23:12:04 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/online_groceries/</guid>
      <description>Online order handling system that uses .txt file to structure data and use it later to create an invoice.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Search Engine</title>
      <link>/projects/search_engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 21:55:38 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/search_engine/</guid>
      <description>Simple search engine for url that can find all links, links to images, count words, display word occurrence table, etc.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:55:11 -0600</pubDate>

      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Vadim Pidoshva. I&amp;rsquo;m originally from Enerhodar, Ukraine 🇺🇦.
I enjoy coding, camping, and skiing on my free time.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UVSim</title>
      <link>/projects/uvsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/projects/uvsim/</guid>
      <description>Program that uses simple instructions in order to simulate machine language operations.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
